



I am an Italian architect, with 4 years of experience. I have worked on different architecture scales, such as urban planning and interior design and have contributed to some international competitions.

I recently carried out a Postgraduate master's degree in Web Design, which is a great passion of mine.

The experiences gained abroad have allowed me to develop good teamwork and organizational skills.

### You can find my portfolio at www.valerialovato.com

### education

2018 - 2019	UOC-Universitat Oberta de Catalunya   Barcelona, Spain Web Design Postgraduate diploma
2013 - 2016	Politecnico di Milano   Milan, Italy  Master degree  Universidade Técnica de Lisboa, Erasmus+  Universidad San Pablo CEU de Madrid, thesis project
2009 - 2012	IUAV Università di Venezia   Venice, Italy Bachelor degree

# working experience

2018 - 2020 Estudi Pep Boada | Hostalric, Spain

Architect

- Project monitoring from the conceptualization to the construction phase.
- Technical drawings, installations blueprints, 3D modelling, rendering and mockups.
- Design of details and constructive solutions.
- · Budgeting and project measurements.
- Meeting with clients and presentation of the proposal.
- Assistance on the work site.
- · Management of contacts with providers.
- · Energy certificate and certificate of habitability.

#### 2017 - 2018 Carles Enrich | Barcelona, España

Architect

- Participation in conceptualization, preliminary design, basic design and construction phase
- Participation in the Master Plan of Rec Comtal for the City Hall of Barcelona
- Participation in international architecture contests
- Development of 2D and 3D graphic material and renderings.

2016 - 2017 Studio Pekka - Archi3o | 's-Hertogenbosch, Netherlands

Architecture internship

- Participation in the schematic design and design development phases
- Assistance in a participative design for a co-housing project
- Development of 2D and 3D graphic material with BIM software
- Video editing for the publication of the book "Goodbye Architecture The architecture of Crematoria in Europe"

2015 (3 meses) PR - Arquitectura Global | Lisbon, Portugal

Architecture internship

## language skills

native Italian

other languages Spanish, English, Catalan, Portugues (intermediate),

French (beginner)

certificates IELTS Advanced

Curso de español Escuela San Pablo CEU: C1

## technical skills

digital modeling Archicad, Revit, Rhinoceros, Sketchup Pro

rendering Vray for Rhinoceros / Sketchup

graphics Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Premiere Pro

others skills Photography, web design